starfinancial.com 2010-12-30

# STAR - Privacy Notice

Important Information Regarding Your Privacy

At STAR Financial Bank, the basis of each client relationship is trust. You have chosen to do business with STAR, and we are committed to honoring that relationship with great care, beginning with the information you have chosen to share with us. We value your trust, and we recognize you have a right to expect your personal financial information to remain private and secure. At the same time, we want to offer you the array of financial products and services you need to accomplish your financial goals. We believe we can do both through the Privacy Policy outlined below. 

What Information We Collect

STAR only collects and maintains the information necessary to administer your business with us and to advise you about our products and services and other opportunities that we feel may be of interest to you. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

• Information we receive from you on applications or other forms;

• Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others; and

• Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency. 

What Information We Disclose

We may disclose all of the information that we collect with affiliated or nonaffiliated companies: 1) if you, our customer, requests or authorizes it; 2) if the information is provided to help complete a transaction initiated by you; 3) if the information is provided to a reputable credit bureau or similar information reporting agency; 4) that perform marketing services on our behalf; 5) with whom we have joint marketing agreements; and 6) if the disclosure is required by law or our regulators. 

We may disclose the following kinds of nonpublic personal information about you:

• Information we receive from you on applications or other forms, such as your name, address and social security number;

• Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance, payment history and parties to transactions. 

We may disclose to the following types of non-affiliated companies:

• Financial service providers such as mortgage bankers, securities broker-dealers and insurance agents;

• As permitted by law. 

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. 

If you prefer that we do not disclose nonpublic personal information about you to nonaffiliated third parties, you may opt out of those disclosures, which you may direct us not to make those disclosures (other than disclosures permitted by law). If you wish to opt out of disclosures to nonaffiliated third parties, you may call your local STAR Financial Bank office at the number listed below to reach our Customer Service Department. 

Anderson, IN (765) 622-4107

Angola, IN (260) 665-2151 

Columbia City, IN (260) 248-6007

Elwood, IN (765) 552-4507

Fort Wayne, IN (260) 467-5507

Greenfield, IN (317) 467-7607

Hamilton, IN (260) 488-2119

Indianapolis, IN (317) 816-2907

Kendallville, IN (260) 349-3730  
Kokomo, IN (765) 868-3807 

Marion, IN (765) 651-6807

Muncie, IN (765) 751-3507

New Castle, IN (765) 593-5107 

If you are outside of a STAR local service area, call our toll-free number at 888-395-2447. Or e-mail us at [customer.service@starfinancial.com](mailto:customer.service@starfinancial.com). 

If you choose to opt out of the sharing of personal information with companies or organizations outside the STAR Financial Bank family, we will not share any personal information about you for any accounts that you may have with us, except as permitted by law. For any accounts or loans that you hold jointly with another person, each person may separately opt out and joint account holders may opt out for each other. If only one joint account holder opts out, we may share information about other joint account holders. Choosing to opt out of this information sharing may limit opportunities for you to receive product and service information that may interest you. 

How We Protect Your Information

STAR safeguards, according to our strict standards of confidentiality, any information our customers share with us. Customer records are securely stored at all times. We continuously strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. Should you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please notify us. We will investigate your concerns and correct any inaccuracies. 

Access to nonpublic, personal information is limited to employees with a valid business reason for having such access. Employees are trained to understand and comply with our information principles, and any employee who violates our Privacy Policy will be subject to disciplinary action. 

When it comes to sharing customer information with nonaffiliated companies, STAR places strict limits on who receives specific information about customer accounts or other personally identifiable data. To protect your privacy, we only work with companies that agree to safeguard your information and to use that information only for the intended purpose. We do not permit these companies to sell to other third parties the information we provide to them. 

What You Can Expect From STAR

We will inform you of our Privacy Policy initially and annually of how to remove your name from our marketing lists. You may contact us to remove your name from our lists at any time by calling your local STAR Financial Bank office and asking for our Customer Service Department. If you have any questions about STAR’s Privacy Policy, please contact us. 

You Can Help

Protect your account numbers, PINs (personal identification numbers) and passwords. NEVER keep your PIN with your debit, ATM or credit cards. If your card is lost or stolen, thieves will try the numbers they find in your wallet or billfold in an attempt to access your accounts. 

Be careful about disclosing your account numbers, your social security number and any other personal numbers to others. If someone calls you, claiming to be the bank and asking for your account number—do not respond. A bank representative will have access to your information and will not need to ask for it. 

Keep your information current. If we suspect fraudulent or unauthorized activity on your account, we will attempt to contact you immediately. Please inform us of changes in your address or phone number. 

Hyperlink Disclaimer At certain places in this site, links to other web sites can be accessed. Links to other Internet sites are provided as a convenience only. These sites contain information created, published, and maintained by organizations independent of STAR Financial Bank.

We do not endorse, approve, certify or control these web sites or the opinions, information, products or services contained therein, and do not guarantee the accuracy, completeness, efficacy or timeliness of information located therein, or at any link contained in a linked site. Internet locations change frequently, so many of the links provided on this web site may no longer access the external web sites listed herein.

|  |   
---|---|---
